Privacy Policy
--------------

_Last updated on 22th January 2023_

_You can find an archive of our previous privacy policies [here](https://cakey.bot/archive/)._

### 1\. Overview

This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the service and tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.

We use your Personal Data to provide and improve the service. By using the service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We regularly review this Privacy Policy and make sure that we process your information in ways that comply with it.

### 2\. Types of Personal Data Collected

While using Our service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information will be requested when needed and will never be collected automatically without your consent.

You do not have to provide any personal data to be able to use our Discord Bot or to browse the website. We only require this information when you are making a purchase.

We do not use cookies or similar tracking technology. We also do not use advertisements or third-party tools that are known to track users. We also do not collect or store your IP address or location data.

### 3\. Use of Personal Data

Cakey Bot may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

* **To provide and maintain our service**, including to monitor the usage of our service.
    
* **For the performance of a contract:** the development, compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the service.
    
* **To contact you:** by email or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application's push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation. (We will not use this for marketing or advertising)
    
* **For business transfers:** We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

Your personal data will not be used for automated decision-making, including profiling.

### 4\. Retention of Personal Data

Cakey Bot will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

### 5\. Transfer of Personal Data

Your information, including Personal Data, is processed on Cakey Bot's servers and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Cakey Bot will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### 6\. Disclosure of Personal Data

##### Business Transactions

If Cakey Bot is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

##### Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Cakey Bot may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

##### Other Legal Requirements

Cakey Bot may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with a legal obligation
    
* Protect and defend the rights or property of Cakey Bot
    
* Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the service
    
* Protect the personal safety of users of Cakey Bot or the public
    
* Protect against legal liability

and where this cannot be reasonably resisted.

### 7\. Security of Personal Data

The security of your Personal Data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

In the event we experience a breach of security, we will promptly notify you if your personal information has been compromised, in accordance with applicable law.

### 8\. Do Not Sell my Personal Information

We do not sell personal information.

### 9\. Processing my Personal Information

We may provide paid products and/or services within the service. In that case, we may use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

* **Stripe**  
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/us/privacy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy)
    
* **PayPal**  
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

### 10\. Links to Other Websites

Our service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### 11\. Data Deletion & Exporting

You can request access to your personal information, or correct or update out-of-date or inaccurate personal information we hold about you by [\[email protected\]](https://cakey.bot/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). You can also request deletion of any personal data we hold on you by [\[email protected\]](https://cakey.bot/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### 12\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on our [Discord server](https://cakey.bot/discord) and update the "Last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any changes a week in advance.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### 13\. How Can I Contact You?

If you have specific questions or feedback about our privacy policy you can [\[email protected\]](https://cakey.bot/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

© 2016-2024 ~ MrCakeSlayer [Add to Server](https://cakey.bot/invite) [Terms of Service](https://cakey.bot/terms.html) | [Privacy Policy](https://cakey.bot/privacy.html)
